You will forget who you danced with at the ball, and marry the girl who fits the slipper...
你将忘记和你在舞厅跳舞的那个女孩  今晚你将迎娶眼前这个穿上舞鞋的女孩
...tonight. Bibbidi-bobbidi-boo.
神奇大变身
Wait. Hold the trumpet! It's all coming back.
等下 我想起来了  我都想起来了
It is you.
是你
Please. Please tell me your name.
拜托 请你告诉我你的名字
It's... Anastasia.
是阿纳斯塔西娅
Anastasia.
阿纳斯塔西娅
Well, I... I know it's sudden, but will you marry me?
我  我知道这很突然  但是你愿意嫁给我么
Yes! Yippee! Ah!
是的 耶  啊
Yes. Er... I... I mean, yes.
是的 呃  我是说 是的
Definitely yes. I will marry you.
我愿意  我愿意嫁给你
Excellent. The ceremony will take place tonight. I trust that meets with your approval, sire.
太好了  婚礼今晚举行  我相信你不会反对的 殿下
The sooner the better.
越快越好
Splendid. Then tonight we will have a new princess.
很好 今晚我们将会有一个新的公主
Wonderful. I'll go tell my father.
棒极了 我去告诉我的父王
Not good! We have to find Cinderelly, Gus Gus!
不妙  我们要找到灰姑娘  格斯 格斯